wooplr.com 2014-02-09

# Wooplr | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

The terms "we", "us", "site" and "Wooplr" refer to www.wooplr.com . When you use wooplr.com , you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Account Registration

You are required to register with a valid Facebook account (using Facebook Connect) before you can post any information on wooplr.com . By using Facebook Connect to sign up at Wooplr, we request for access to your personal information including your name, email address, likes, friend list, birthday and profile photo. This data is used to help us better understand the things you might be interested in. It also helps us to provide more relevant information on your Wooplr stream based on your interests. We never post to your facebook profile without your explicit consent. Also, you can revoke Wooplr's access to your Facebook account at anytime through Facebook's privacy settings.

Communication with You

We use your Personal Information to contact you with Wooplr newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You can choose to unsubscribe from such communication through your account settings. We never spam our users.

Public Consumption

All information submitted by you on Wooplr.com including but not limited to recommendations, photos, comments on recommendations, your follower/following list, profile information (including your first and last names - and if you choose to provide additional Personal Information such as your 'About Me' section, personal web site link, your facebook & twitter profile links, location, but excluding your other account registration information - will be displayed), and other content you post to wooplr.com are meant for public consumption. We may display this content on wooplr.com , and further distribute it to a wider audience through third party sites and services. It is to be noted that providing additional Personal Information is voluntary. We recommend that you guard and refrain from disclosing any information you consider sensitive and confidential.Currently, you need to be a registered user of Wooplr to post and engage with the content on the site.

Changing or Deleting Information & Account Termination

All Users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their User account by contacting us or by editing their profile via the site. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. At the moment, you cannot delete recommendations made on Wooplr. However, you can modify the certain parts of the recommendations you submitted. Currently, there is no option to delete your Wooplr account once it has been created.

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our use of your information and will be located here. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on wooplr.com prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use wooplr.com after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
